

Kamil Dróżdż Front-end Developer

My Contact



+48 570728479



Warsaw



https://kamildrozdz.pl



Skills

★☆☆☆ React

★★☆☆ HTML(Metodology BEM)

★★☆☆ CSS(SASS, Tailwind)

★★★☆☆ Git

★★★☆☆ JavaScript

★★☆☆ GitHub

★★★☆☆ RWD

★★☆☆☆ SEO

★★★☆☆ WordPress ★★★☆ Active Listening

 $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Leftrightarrow$ The ability to share knowledge

★★ ★★☆ Willingness to constantly learn

Achievements

Programming with JavaScript, Coursera

October 2022

Introduction to Front-End Development, Coursera

October 2022

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, FreeCodeCamp

October 2022

Certyficate EF SET™, The EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

October 2022

Course basic Javascript, Udemy

September 2022

Increase SEO Traffic with WordPress, Coursera

October 2022

About Me

My goal is to gain experience in programming, develop organizational and future managerial skills. I want to improve towards Front-end programming, learn from the best, broaden my horizons through courses, trainings, guides, but also by doing my own projects, under the watchful eye of experienced programmers.

My story began with the desire to create a website based on Wordpress. After starting it, I felt unsatisfied. I found that I wanted more interference in its appearance than just using someone else's templates. Independent programming, design and the entire web development process give me great joy and I would like to develop further.

Therefore, I am very interested in working permanently in a company with extensive programming experience.

Social Profiles

- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- **Github**
- **Portfolio website**

Experience

Performer at Polski standard, Warsaw

March 2018 - current

- · Acquiring orders,
- Performing orders and picking up with the customer,
- · Keeping in touch with customers,
- · Creating offers,
- · Team management,
- · Creating a website in Wordpress,
- · Modernizing and updating the website,
- · Accounting,
- · Work schedule,
- Negotiations and discussions with clients.

Health and safety worker at Twence B.V, Hengelo

August 2017 - April 2018

- · Knowledge of labor law and OHS provisions,
- · Responsibility for colleagues during the joint work,
- · Working under time pressure,
- Keeping the workplace clean,
- Team management, supervision over entrusted tasks.

Laundryman at Wasserij Engelbertink, Oldenzaal

June 2017 - August 2017 (summer job)

- · Sorting clothes, bedding,
- · Preparing laundry for washing,
- · Folding, packing clothes, bedding,
- Operation of washing machines, ironers etc.

Production worker at Wolters B.V, Enter

July 2016 - September 2016 (summer job)

- · Palletizing according to the pattern,
- · Quality control,
- Maintaining the cleanliness of the station,
- Receiving the finished product,
- Teamwork.

Production worker at Europe Retial Packing, Den Haag

June 2015 – September 2015 (summer job)

- · Palletizing according to the pattern,
- Quality control,
- Ensuring compliance with health and safety regulations,
- · Close cooperation with management,
- · Direct participation in the work of the brigade,
- · Motivating and ensuring team development,
- · Reporting current activities,
- Securing pallets,
- Notifying superiors about faults,
- · Safely operated all equipment and tools.

Education Background

2013 - 2017

Technical School in Lipno, Lipno Education level: secondary

Specialization: Construction Technician

2019-2021

Non-public General Secondary School for Adults in Zielonka, Zielonka Education level: secondary

Specialization: Health and Safety